{
  "non-prof": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "While driving, you should look at your side and rear view mirror:",
      "choices": [
        "Quickly",
        "If you want",
        "Not less than once per one minute"
      ],
      "correct": "Quickly"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "You can overtake in the right side of your vehicle if:",
      "choices": [
        "The road has two or more lanes going in one direction",
        "The road is two-way",
        "The sidewalk is wide"
      ],
      "correct": "The road has two or more lanes going in one direction"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "A person who drives while under influence of alcohol or drugs is punishable by law with:",
      "choices": [
        "Suspension of license",
        "All answers are correct",
        "Fines and imprisonment"
      ],
      "correct": "All answers are correct"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Before leaving the parking area, you should: ",
      "choices": ["Look around first", "Sound your horn ", "Immediately go "],
      "correct": "Look around first"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "The minimum age in the application for Non-Professional Driver’s License is: ",
      "choices": ["18 years old", "16 years old", "17 years old"],
      "correct": "17 years old"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "After overtaking, you want to safely go back to the lane where you where you came from, you should",
      "choices": [
        "Use the rear view mirror to check the vehicle you have overtaken",
        "Look at the vehicle you have overtaken by turning your head",
        "Stop"
      ],
      "correct": "Use the rear view mirror to check the vehicle you have overtaken"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Obtaining a driver’s license is:",
      "choices": ["An honor", "A privilege", "A right"],
      "correct": "A privilege"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "In an intersection with a STOP sign, you should:",
      "choices": [
        "Slow down and proceed if there is no danger",
        "Stop and proceed if there is no danger",
        "Give way to vehicles going from left and right, proceed if there is no danger"
      ],
      "correct": "Stop and proceed if there is no danger"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "A Non-Professional driver’s license is suited for:",
      "choices": [
        "Private vehicles",
        "Public utility vehicles",
        "All types of vehicles"
      ],
      "correct": "Private vehicles"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What should you prepare for a long trip?",
      "choices": [
        "Prepare the necessary tools that can be used to repair the vehicle",
        "Plan your route and make sure the vehicle is running in good condition",
        "All answers are correct"
      ],
      "correct": "All answers are correct"
    }
  ]
}
